Andres Felipe Orozco Jaramillo

Software Developer

+1 631 459 8183 | andres.orozco.dev@gmail.com

RESUME

Software developer with over 3 years of experience in Full Stack projects. Led the development of scalable solutions at Team Tech Solutions, improving performance and efficiency through modern development practices such as CI/CD, FastAPI, React, and Angular.

EXPERIENCE

TEAM TECH SOLUTIONS

Software Developer

April 2023 - January 2024 - Miami, United States

- Developed web applications based on FastAPI, Angular, and React for financial capitalization services.
- Improved application performance by optimizing module loading by 40% and enhanced backend HTTP service response processes by 20%.
- Led CI/CD practices to improve software delivery efficiency.

SISTECREDITO

Software Developer

July 2020 - March 2022 - Medellín, Colombia

- Developed web applications based on Angular to manage business associations and basic services.
- Improved user experience by implementing intuitive and responsive interfaces adaptable to all screen sizes.
- Implemented high-quality code, achieving 80% test coverage across all projects and improving module loading by 40%.

MULTIMEDIA LAB

Software Developer

January 2020 - July 2020 - Medellin, Colombia

 Collaborated in the development of web applications using Angular, React, React Native, and WordPress.

SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Typescript, Angular, React.js, Tailwindcss, Bootstrap, Python, FastAPI, Node.js, Express.js, RESTful API, SQL, NoSQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Firebase, SQLite, Git, GitHub, Docker, Azure and SCRUM.

EDUCATION

Universidad de Medellin

2015 - 2021

Bachelor's in System Engineering.